Finding Aid for Ivory Photo, Ann Arbor, Michigan ca. 1927-1971
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Negatives-- 4"x5"
  - University of Michigan
    - Individuals and Groups
      - Administration
        - Presidents
          - Ruthven, Alexander
            - Ruthven and others (Spencer) 1945 (Box 21)
            - With horse December 16, 1959, 2 negatives (Box 21)
      - Alumni
        - Elbel, Louis. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Student Life -- Bands Marching)
        - Hopwood, Avery 1905 portrait (Box 21)
      - Faculty
        - Abbot, Waldo. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Colleges, Schools, and Other Divisions, Broadcasting Service)
        - Anderson, Leigh -- Chemistry Department February 6, 1968, 5 negatives (Box 21)
        - Brown, Marilyn Mason. (Box 21)
          (See: Mason, Marilyn)
        - Carruth, Hayden K. -- Speech 1952, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Chenea, Paul F. -- Engineering Mechanics 1952, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Coller, Frederick A. -- Surgery November 10, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 21)
        - Cowden, Roy W. -- Rhetoric, portrait (painting) (Box 21)
        - Crisler, Fritz. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Student Life, Athletics)
        - Cross, Arthur Lyon -- History; and unidentified woman February 3, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 21)
          [see also 8"x10" negative]
        - Davis, Sarita. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Colleges, Education School, University Elementary School)
        - Davis, Professor -- passport photo October 1938 (Box 21)
        - Densmore, Gail Ernest -- Speech Department (with family) September 13, 1953 (Box 21)
        - Francis, D. Thomas, Jr. -- Epidemiology December 12, 1945 (Box 21)
        - Greenman, Emerson F. -- Museum of Anthropology July 1, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Hayes, Professor -- unidentified group 1952 (Box 21)
        - Killinger, Dr. -- Bacteriology October 13, 1937 (Box 21)
        - Lewis, Dr. Howard B. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Colleges, Department of Biological Chemistry)
        - Lopez, Carlos -- Drawing and Painting -- unidentified group, 1949. (Box 21)
          (See also: UM Colleges, Schools and Other Divisions, Architecture and Design)
        - Losh, Hazel M. -- Astronomy October 26, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Lyons, Chalmers John -- Dentistry (bust) June 14, 1937 (Box 21)
        - McCord, Dr. Carey P. -- Medical School and School of Public Health May 22, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Madely, Dr. Joseph E. -- Music 1948, 3 negatives (Box 21)
        - Maier, Norman. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Colleges, Schools and Other Divisions, Psychology Department)
        - Mann, Matt. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Colleges, Schools and Other Divisions -- Psychology Department)
        - Mason, Marilyn -- Assistant Professor of Organ June 15, 1957, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Moore, George R. -- Dentistry 1949 (Box 21)
        - Oosterbaan, Benny. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Athletics -- Football)
        - Plumer, James -- Institute of Fine Arts, Fall 1938 (Box 21)
        - Randall, Harrison M. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Buildings -- Physics)
        - Revelli, William -- Music (with George Roach) April 21, 1940 (Box 21)
        - Slosson, Preston -- History 1948, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Stahl, Otto -- Music February 16, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Tracy, Professor -- with family September 14, 1950 (Box 21)
        - Van Duren, Arthur -- Counselors' Office and Germanic Languages circa 1946 (Box 21)
        - Vaughan, Henry -- Public Health
          - Portraits circa 1955, 2 negatives (Box 21)
          - Unidentified house, 19th century (Box 21)
        - Walter, Erich -- English 1946, 3 negatives (Box 21)
        - Wolaver, Earl S. -- Law January 18, 1937 (Box 21)
        - Yntema, Hessel E. -- Law March 16, 1940 (Box 21)
        - Miscellaneous: unidentified, 7 negatives (Box 21)
      - Regents
        - Beal, Junius September 22, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 21)
        - Kipke, Harry. (Box 21)
          (See: UM -- Athletics -- Football)
      - Staff
        - Bietham, Susan -- Head Librarian, Medical Library May 10, 1951, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Michigan Union Kitchen staff circa 1937 (Box 21)
        - Nelson, J. Raleigh -- Director, International Center (painted portrait) May 12, 1943 (Box 21)
        - Shaw, Wilfred B. -- Director of Alumni Relations circa 1938 (Box 21)
        - Soop, Everett. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Buildings and Views -- Rackham Educational Memorial, Detroit)
        - Tapping, T. Hawley -- General Secretary, Alumni Association
          - With Teddy and polo ponies April 30, 1938, 6 negatives (Box 21)
          - Tapping, his wife, unidentified man, and dog circa 1938, 4 negatives (Box 21)
          - Mrs. T. Hawley Tapping at home circa 1940, 4 negatives (Box 21)
          - Tapping and his wife at home November 15, 1962, 3 negatives (Box 21)
        - Thomas, Lorenzo D. -- Superintendent of Athletic Buildings and Grounds -- grounds crew, Intramural Building April 19, 1937, 8 negatives (Box 21)
      - Students
        - Baldwin, Bill January 26, 1941 (Box 21)
        - Call, Mary (or Mary Enders) May 16, 1939 (Box 21)
        - Carrothers (at Senior Ball) June 21, 1941 (Box 21)
        - Enders, Mary (or Mary Call) May 16, 1939 (Box 21)
        - Goldcamp, Richard
          - March 16, 1937 (Box 21)
          - April 23, 1937 (Box 21)
        - Hammett, Harriett May 16, 1939 (Box 21)
        - Van Buskirk (Edgar F., Jr.) February 10, 1938 (Box 21)
        - Walkley, Arland R. November 24, 1939 (Box 21)
        - Warner, Bob December 12, 1941 (Box 21)
        - Wistert, Francis M. (law student) September 26, 1938, 5 negatives (Box 21)
        - Wixson (Joseph A. or Richard) January 5, 1937 (Box 21)
        - Wynn, George H. (Medical School graduate) June 21, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 21)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Army officers November 11, 1933 (Box 21)
        - Barden -- passport photo February 27, 1940 (Box 21)
        - Bigelow -- June 19, 1940 (Box 21)
        - Blakeman, Edward W. April 1, 1937 (Box 21)
        - Briggs, Robert W. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Buildings and Views -- Haven Hall fire 1950)
        - College Education group July 17, 1937 (Box 21)
        - Dakin and family circa 1948, 5 negatives (Box 21)
        - Dawson, Mr. September 15, 1950 (Box 21)
        - Dimitroff, Boris January 16, 1940 (Box 21)
        - Drake, Dr. -- with group October 1952 (Box 21)
        - Finkbeiner, Caroline -- with group of women November 8, 1948 (Box 21)
        - French, Dick circa 1940 (Box 21)
        - Halford, Mr. -- group of men in Michigan Union June 6, 1953 (Box 21)
        - Hall, Dr. (oil portrait) circa 1938 (Box 21)
        - Hartwell, Wayne. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Buildings and Views, Burton Tower)
        - Hildner, Dr. -- conducting and playing piano February 24, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Huber, Dean -- oil portrait May 3, 1932 (Box 21)
        - Kessler, Mr. 1946 (Box 21)
        - Kretchmar, Mr. -- group of men September 26, 1956 (Box 21)
        - Latin America group May 20, 1942 (Box 21)
        - Lemon, Dr. -- retirement party 1952, 5 negatives (Box 21)
        - Murphy, Frank. (Box 21)
          (See: UM Special Celebrations and Events -- Ruthven Pageant)
          (See: UM Athletics -- Football -- Fielding Yost)
        - Odle, Henry W. -- Associate Editor, Burroughs Clearinghouse, Detroit -- for Professor McCracken 1949, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Phoenix Project Executive Committee 1950 (Ruthven and others), 3 negatives (Box 21)
        - Smith, Dr. B. 1953 (Box 21)
        - Untermeyer, Louis (poet-guest lecturer) -- at railroad depot March 20, 1939, 4 negatives (Box 21)
        - Wendel family August 19, 1957 (Box 21)
        - White, Sam. (Box 21)
          (See: UM -- Alumni Activities -- Miscellaneous)
        - Williams, G. Mennen. (Box 21)
        - Wilson, Professor -- post-graduate course April 9, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 21)
      - Organizations
        - American Society of Civil Engineers -- group photo March 29, 1956 (Box 21)
        - Emeritus Club
          - Reunion -- group photo June 1947 (Box 21)
          - Waterman gym -- 1949, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Hayri -- Turkish Society -- group photo 1949 (Box 21)
        - M Club -- officers circa 1948, 5 negatives (Box 21)
        - Michigan Engineering Society 1951, 2 negatives (Box 21)
        - Michigan Music Appreciation Committee May 8, 1940, 7 negatives (Box 21)
    - Special Celebrations and Events
      - Book Fair October 25, 1938, 3 negatives (Box 22)
      - Centennial, UM: Community Banquet June 14, 1937 (Box 22)
      - Christmas Party, Mrs. Simon's --(sorority or League House) December 23, 1941 (Box 22)
      - Christmas Sing, Hill Auditorium 1952 (Box 22)
      - Commencement
        - Ferry Field circa 1930 (Box 22)
        - circa 1937, 7 negatives (Box 22)
        - Procession circa 1938 (Box 22)
        - Steps at Angell Hall circa 1939 (Box 22)
        - Honorary degree recipients June 17, 1939, 4 negatives (Box 22)
        - Ferry Field 1939, 3 negatives (Box 22)
        - Hill Auditorium circa 1940, 2 negatives (Box 22)
        - June 20/21 1941, 7 negatives (Box 22)
        - George Fink (Kudo) June 21, 1941 (Box 22)
        - June 1947, 3 negatives (Box 22)
        - 1950, 2 negatives (Box 22)
      - Conferences
        - Extension Service -- Rackham 1951, 2 negatives (Box 22)
        - Michigan Life (Jean Picard, Charles F. Kettering) November 1, 1939, 5 negatives (Box 22)
        - United Health and Welfare Foundation -- Michigan Union May 21, 1953, 5 negatives (Box 22)
      - Exhibit, Photography circa 1936 (Box 22)
      - M Banquet -- 3rd Annual 1952, 16 negatives (Box 22)
      - Michigan League -- Tea for Freshman Girls (Mrs. Ruthven, Mrs. Conger) September 20, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 22)
      - May Festival (Lily Pons, Szigeti) May 10, 1940, 5 negatives (Box 22)
      - Ruthven Pageant (includes Alexander Ruthven and Frank Murphy photos) October 22, 1939, 16 negatives (Box 22)
      - Yost (Fielding) Banquet. (Box 22)
        (See: UM Athletics -- Football -- Coaches)
    - Student Life
      - ASPA (Mrs. Bidwell) -- group photo circa 1948 (Box 22)
      - American Student Union (Harold Norris, Margaret Campbell) December 6, 1960, 2 negatives (Box 22)
      - Band, Marching
        - At football game (Alexander Ruthven watching) 1930, 5 negatives (Box 22)
        - At football game, block M formation 1930s (Box 22)
        - In front of Angell Hall circa 1930s (Box 22)
        - "Phil and gals" November 12, 1938, 4 negatives (Box 22)
        - Michigan-Michigan State football game, band formations October 5, 1940, 6 negatives (Box 22)
        - Football game, Louis Elbel conducting 1948 (Box 22)
      - Bands, University
        - April 9, 1941, 13 negatives (Box 22)
          [see also 8"x10" prints]
        - 1958 (Box 22)
        - In Harris Hall March 15, 1958 (Box 22)
      - Black Friday
        - November 1, 1938 (Box 22)
        - November 17, 1939, 4 negatives (Box 22)
          (Michigan Theater)
      - Bunyan (Paul) Ball 1948-1949, 4 negatives (Box 22)
      - Chinese Students Club (group photo) January 7, 1956 (Box 22)
      - Chorus, Girls' March 16, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 22)
      - Dance Concert 1930, 10 negatives (Box 22)
      - Dances
        (See also: J-Hop)
        - Bill Sawyer's Orchestra February 9, 1940, 14 negatives (Box 22)
        - Bill Sawyer's Orchestra truck December 1, 1940, 2 negatives (Box 22)
        - Tom Snyder's Orchestra December 1, 1940 (Box 22)
        - Sawyer Orchestra January 11, 1941 (Box 22)
        - Bill Sawyer Orchestra May 22, 1941, 4 negatives (Box 22)
        - Bill Sawyer's Orchestra in Michigan Union October 3, 1942, 5 negatives (Box 22)
        - Jerry Edwards Orchestra January 11, 1946 (Box 22)
      - Fraternities and Sororities
        - Alpha Chi Omega -- girls and ducks March 29, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 22)
        - Alpha Tau Delta -- young women in house ("Simpson Influence") December 6, 1936, 4 negatives (Box 22)
        - Alpha Tau Omega ("Prize Winner" -- sculpture?) October 16, 1937 (Box 22)
        - Beta Sigma Phi -- group photos
          - circa 1940 (Box 22)
          - circa 1948 (Box 22)
          - 1949, 3 negatives (Box 22)
        - Chi Psi
          (See also: Ann Arbor Buildings -- 1705 Washtenaw)
          - Group photo January 10, 1946 (Box 22)
          - Interior wall with portraits circa April 1955 (H. Seger Slifer) (Box 22)
        - Delta Delta Delta -- interiors with Mrs. Schilling and sorority girls October 1, 1939, 7 negatives (Box 22)
          [See also: Ann Arbor Buildings -- 718 Tappan]
        - Delta Sigma Delta
          - Reunion group June 8, 1954, 4 negatives (Box 22)
          - Drs. Charles P. Weinrich and William Cleland, founders, with plaques June 10, 1954, 3 negatives (Box 22)
        - Delta Upsilon -- group photo (Don Calhoun) 1948 (Box 22)
        - Gamma Alpha -- group photo December 1950 (Box 22)
        - Kappa Alpha Theta
          - J-Hop Committee circa 1952 (Box 22)
          - Group photo of sorority members December 11, 1956 (Box 22)
        - Kappa Delta -- girls smoking pipes May 19, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 22)
        - Kappa Kappa Psi, group photo 1950 (Box 22)
        - Phi Delta Theta -- house with students May 15, 1937, 12 negatives (Box 22)
        - Phi Mu Alpha, group photo 1948 (Box 22)
        - Pi Beta Phi
          - Exterior and interiors with sorority girls May 21, 1937, 7 negatives (Box 22)
          - Sorority girls 1951, 4 negatives (Box 22)
        - Sigma Chi and Phi Kappa Psi -- speedball finals November 20, 1939, 2 negatives (Box 22)
        - Sigma Chi and Alpha Delta Phi parking sign circa 1940 (Box 22)
        - Sigma Rho Tau -- group photos
          - Debaters May 9, 1940 (Box 22)
          - April 16, 1942 (Box 22)
          - 1948, 2 negatives (Box 22)
        - Sigma Sigma Phi - interior with Asian women May 20, 1935, 2 negatives (Box 22)
        - Tau Delta Phi -- 44th Convention banner circa 1956 (Box 22)
        - Zeta Beta Tau. (Box 22)
          (See: Ann Arbor Buildings -- 2006 Washtenaw)
      - Glee Club (girls') February 13, 1943 (Box 22)
      - Hillel
        - Hillel Jamboree November 29, 1941, 10 negatives (Box 22)
        - Hillel Foundation -- unidentified portraits December 8, 1941, 9 negatives (Box 22)
        - Passover Seder April 1, 1942 (Box 22)
        - Hillelzapoppin' April 24, 1942, 6 negatives (Box 22)
        - Banquet circa 1942-1943 (Box 22)
        - Red Cross work November 18, 1943 (Box 22)
      - Homecoming
        - Decorations (Sigma Chi and other houses) October 24, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 22)
        - Decorations (Sigma Chi and other houses) October 28, 1939, 5 negatives (Box 22)
        - Decorations -- 1601 Washtenaw October 19, 1940 (Box 22)
        - undated, 5 negatives (Box 22)
      - International Banquet, Michigan Union November 24, 1937, 5 negatives (Box 22)
      - International Center
        - Banquet performance December 10, 1938, 6 negatives (Box 22)
        - December 18, 1942 (Box 22)
      - J-Hop
        - Group circa 1939 (Box 22)
        - Governor Van Wagoner and others February 14, 1941, 7 negatives (Box 22)
      - Mardi Gras May 4, 1938 (Box 22)
      - Michigamua May 27, 1937, 5 negatives (Box 22)
      - Michigan Daily-- staff at work, May 15, 1937, 17 negatives (Box 22)
      - Michigan Wolverine Student Co-op, 209 South State, exteriors and interiors with students October 14, 1937, 14 negatives (Box 22)
      - Michigras
        - Preparations April 23, 1937, 8 negatives (Box 22)
        - April 24, 1937, 4 negatives (Box 22)
        - May 1937, 5 negatives (Box 23)
        - 1937 (Box 23)
      - Newman Club -- group, October 21 1941 (Box 23)
      - One-Act Play March 16, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - Ping Pong (woman playing) August 16, 1934 (Box 23)
      - Pretzel Bell Restaurant -- interior circa 1942 (Box 23)
      - Senior Ball -- committee, in car April 28, 1942 (Box 23)
      - Soph Cabaret rehearsals? and portraits November 17, 1937, 15 negatives (Box 23)
      - Swing-out May 23, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 23)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Rally on Diag, "Sacrifice for Spain - Progressive club 1930s, 2 negatives (Box 23)
        - Presidential election poll table 1932 (Box 23)
        - Girls playing ping pong August 16, 1934 (Box 23)
        - Women students(?) on Campus May 5, 1937, 9 negatives (Box 23)
        - Student hangouts -- Drake's, diag. street scenes May 14, 1937, 14 negatives (Box 23)
        - Students leaving for Christmas break by bus December 15, 1939, 4 negatives (Box 23)
        - First Aid? (Mrs. Brown) -- University News Service March 18, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 23)
        - Johnnie Doolittle and Tokyo raid headlines May 20, 1942, 3 negatives (Box 23)
        - Women students(?) playing cards (Jean Coller -- Ann Arbor News) March 22, 1942 (Box 23)
        - Group of women students circa 1946 (Box 23)
    - World War II
      - Air Force -- CPT Project November 2, 1942, 11 negatives (Box 23)
      - Army
        - Harding Course June 26, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 23)
        - Judge Advocate General's School (JAG)
          - September 24, 1942, 7 negatives (Box 23)
          - Faculty December 4, 1942 (Box 23)
          - General Nolan and others December 6, 1942, 2 negatives (Box 23)
          - Sixth Graduation retreat -- Cramer December 23, 1942, 8 negatives (Box 23)
          - Retreat May 21, 1943, 8 negatives (Box 23)
          - Retreat June 30, 1943, 2 negatives (Box 23)
          - 1943, 7 negatives (Box 23)
        - Memorial Service 1946, 12 negatives (Box 23)
      - Naval ROTC
        - Conant, [Mr.] May 29, 1943, 2 negatives (Box 23)
        - Plaque and photos of NROTC graduates who died in World War II November 5, 1946 (Box 23)
      - Navy: Captain Cassidy December 30, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - Reserve Officers' Training Corps (Captain Vollrath) -- group photo January 13, 1942 (Box 23)
      - University War Board February 21, 1942, 3 negatives (Box 23)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Kahn's display of birds 1952, 2 negatives (Box 23)
  - Bridgewater
    - Bridgewater Machine Tool Company -- interior with workers 1951, 9 negatives (Box 23)
      [see also 5"x7" and 8"x10" negatives]
  - Chelsea
    - Mission (four men) circa 1954, 2 negatives (Box 23)
    - William A. Thomas Company fish scaler February 27, 1955 (Box 23)
    - Blaess Elevator August 20, 1971, 7 negatives (in 4 envelope) (Box 23)
  - Dexter
    - Dexter Public School April 3, 1939 (Box 23)
    - Dexter High School football player October 15, 1953, 2 negatives (Box 23)
    - Dexter Judge -- house renovation 1940, 16 negatives (Box 23)
    - Fram Corporation -- staff, equipment 1949-1956, 16 negatives (Box 23)
    - Michigan Molded Plastics -- employees August 10, 1955, 3 negatives (Box 23)
  - Manchester
    - Double A Products -- sales meeting November 2, 1951 (Box 23)
  - Milan
    - Fire February 16, 1941, 3 negatives (Box 23)
    - U.S. 23 and William Road September 13, 1960, 3 negatives (Box 23)
  - Pittsfield Township
    - Houses under construction 1949-1950, 11 negatives (Box 23)
    - Pittsfield Union range No. 882 -- group photo May 5, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 23)
    - Road scene 1953, 2 negatives (Box 23)
    - Stage Stop Tourist Court (Motel) 1951, 2 negatives (Box 23)
  - Salem Township
    - Rural scenes -- railroad crossings February 20, 1954, 13 negatives (Box 23)
    - Salem's Church and Johnny's Service Station 1949, 3 negatives (Box 23)
  - Saline
    - Gross, W.R., Company -- equipment May 1946, 7 negatives (Box 23)
    - Holmes General Store and road scenes circa 1970, 7 negatives (in 4 envelope) (Box 23)
    - Saline Hardware -- event in gymnasium March 1, 1939 (Box 23)
    - Saline Valley Farms -- interior February 17, 1969, 13 negatives (Box 23)
    - Wedding (with views of church and other buildings) December 29, 1956, 8 negatives (Box 23)
  - Scio Township
    - Salem Evangelical Lutheran Church -- confirmation 1953-1961, 20 negatives (Box 23)
  - Whitmore Lake
    - Haag, Bob, Painting and Decorating -- man and truck circa 1953 (Box 23)
  - Willow Run
    - Willow Run Airport -- planes circa 1949, 2 negatives (Box 23)
  - Ypsilanti
    - Businesses
      - Agda's Delicatessen, 107 West Michigan Avenue circa 1951 (Box 23)
      - Ambassador Laundry, 8-12 South Huron circa 1950 (Box 23)
      - Brikcrete Shop circa 1956, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - Dave's Furniture -- interior circa 1956, 3 negatives (Box 23)
      - Don's Bike Sales, 2755 Michigan Avenue September 1955 (Box 23)
      - Ernie's Place -- restaurant interior circa 1938, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - Fingerle-Hollister Wood and Lumber, 822 East Michigan circa 1960 (Box 23)
      - Food and Drug Mart, 13 North Washington June 1953 (Box 23)
      - Ford Bomber Plant -- under construction July 6, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - Gordon's Grocery, 454 South Huron 1951 (Box 23)
      - Huron Hotel -- exterior and interior April 7, 1939, 5 negatives (Box 23)
      - Jerry Bakery 1951, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - Krueger Hydrolics -- machines March 1954, 3 negatives (Box 23)
      - Mr. Caslin, Justin, Real Estate circa 1956 (Box 23)
      - Obermeyer Oldsmobile, 334 East Michigan Avenue 1954, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - Riley's Market -- exterior and interior July 13, 1953, 3 negatives (Box 23)
      - Roth Cleaners -- advertisement circa 1956 (Box 23)
      - Schmidt Antiques -- interior May 27, 1959, 4 negatives (Box 23)
      - Sport Shop, 106 West Michigan Avenue 1951 (Box 23)
      - Starwas Gulf, Washtenaw and Owendale circa 1960 (Box 23)
      - Taylor Television Service -- truck and interior with employees circa 1956, 3 negatives (Box 23)
      - Trojan Cleaners, 12 West Michigan Avenue circa 1951 (Box 23)
      - Turner, Barton and Malow -- men picketing 1952, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - United Stove Company -- exterior and interior circa 1952, 2 negatives (Box 23)
      - Wallace Books, 311 Brewer 1951 (Box 24)
      - Wood-Williams-Copp Manufacturing Company, trailer hitches 1952-1957, 8 negatives (Box 24)
      - Ypsi-Ecorse Laundry -- machines July 28, 1969 (Box 24)
    - Centennial
      - January 8, 1937, 3 negatives (Box 24)
    - Houses and Apartments
      - Ballard and Driscoll Court circa 1953 (Box 24)
      - Forest, West -- 509 -- Ypsi Odyssey Apartments, early 1960s, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Perrin -- 416-422 -- apartment building circa 1960s, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Thorn Oaks -- 4091 1960s, 2 negatives (Box 24)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Gilbert House (Victorian) circa 1942, 2 negatives (Box 24)
        - Weathertite Homes circa 1956 (Box 24)
        - Unidentified December 3, 1965, 5 negatives (Box 24)
    - People
      - Douglas, Mrs. Wilmot November 4, 1937 (Box 24)
    - Rural Scenes
      - Martz Road 1972 (Box 24)
      - Schultz, Raymond, farm (?) -- 10090 Martz Road, late 1960s, 4 negatives (in 2 envelope) (Box 24)
    - Schools
      - Cleary College
        - Baseball team 1939, 2 negatives (Box 24)
        - Basketball teams 1938-1939, 2 negatives (Box 24)
        - Buildings
          - Classrooms October 22, 1938, 2 negatives (Box 24)
          - Interior recreation area and library with students April 18, 1938, 10 negatives (Box 24)
          - Main building exterior May 6, 1939, 10 negatives (Box 24)
          - Rooming house with students May 10, 1940 (Box 24)
          - Main building May 20, 1941, 5 negatives (Box 24)
          - Main building July 15, 1941, 2 negatives (Box 24)
        - Chorus December 6, 1937, 2 negatives (Box 24)
        - Cleary, P. Roger -- President
          - At home June 18, 1938, 7 negatives (Box 24)
          - Portraits circa 1940, 3 negatives (Box 24)